Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We live in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
It's a...
Flower.
No, it's a person.
Are you sure?
That old man just killed a
great king squid with one shot.
The question is, why?
Was he trying to save us,
or is he just fishing?
You're gonna say anything?
Hey, you want to fight?
We'll fight.
We got cannons back here! You bastard!
You try it and someone's going to die!
Yeah, and who's that?
Me, of course.
Excuse me.
You?
He's up there, bud.
That old bastard's mocking us.
There's a couple things we need to know.
Where are we?
And who are you?
You've got some nerve, stranger.
It's only polite to
introduce yourself before
asking a question of
someone you've just met.
All right, fair enough.
I'll go first.
If you must know,
my name is Crocus, and I'm the
lighthouse keeper of the Twin Capes.
I'm 71 and a half years old, Gemini.
I'm a sword!
You'd like to know where we are,
but your rude behavior leaves me
disinclined to accommodate your curiosity?
except that you are trespassing
on my private resort.
Besides, I think it's pretty obvious,
seeing as how you were eaten.
So you're saying that we
were swallowed by the whale.
But since when does a whale's
stomach have clouds in it?
Wait a minute, if we've been eaten,
what's going to happen to us?
I don't want to be digested!
Stop doing that! What's wrong?
Haven't you ever heard of a running gag?
That was a gag!
The exit is over there.
We can get out!
Okay, even if I believed a whale's
belly could have an exit door?
Nothing's there but sky.
Something's not right here.
Wait, look at the sky.
No Scales. Nothing's moving.
They're painted on.
It's a giant mural inside
the whale's stomach. Huh?
Call it a doctor's playful mind.
You're not making any
sense, you crazy old fool.
Easy, don't let him get to you.
Yeah, just shut up.
Nami, if that is an exit,
then we need to get to it.
Agreed.
Ah, Crate, what now?
It's begun
Look!
That's no island, it's some kind of ship!
It's made of wire!
Yeah, of course!
Because we're floating
on a sea of gastric acid!
That means a wooden ship wouldn't fare
well if it stayed here too long Hey,
what's with this freaky whale?
Answer me, old man!
He's very angry.
These aftershocks are a result of him
hitting his head against the red line.
What?
That explains it?
Why he had such deep
scars on his forehead!
Not to mention all this strange howling!
Why does he do it?
It's because he's suffering.
It's all starting to make sense
so what's the geezer up to?
More than likely he's trying to kill.
The whale from the inside.
It's time.
What a despicable way to kill something.
Okay we've Solved the
mystery of the whale.
Now how about we find a way out
of its belly before it digests us?
We have no right to judge the old
man nor do we need to save the whale.
What we need to do is Focus on
how to get the hell out of here.
We're
never gonna
get anywhere if
the Waves keep searching like this?
How can we escape?
If we can't even move.
Our only Choice is to paddle.
Take the oars.
Whatever it takes.
We have to fight.
Luffy, right away!
I know he's outside!
I caught a glimpse of him
flying out of the whale's mouth!
That old guy just jumped in! Huh?
Is he insane?
The acid will eat him alive!
I'm so dizzy, I'm gonna hurl!
Hey, that's weird.
The whale's got a river inside it, too.
Things are looking up, my dear.
We've been successful so far.
Listen carefully, Miss Wednesday.
Behind these doors lie the beast's stomach,
and that troublesome geezer as well.
He must be eliminated before
he can interfere again.
Remember, it's all for the
whale. Indeed, Mr. Nine.
This whale's a precious creature,
and one that holds the sweet
promise of life for our town.
Guys!
Crocus just resurfaced!
Look, forget about the old guy.
Our focus should be on finding
a way to open these doors.
All right, here's the plan, baby.
Three, two, one, then we
kick through the doors!
Roger that, Mr. Nine.
I'm ready any time.
What is that voice, Mr. Nine?
I don't know, Miss Wednesday.
They're back!
Not good!
We're going to fall into gastric acid!
Luffy?
Zoro, is everyone okay?
So, um...
I can use a hand!
Looks like Luffy's not alone.
Who do you suppose those
two weirdos are with him?
Where'd that old geezer disappear to?
Forget him.
We need to save Luffy.
You've got to stop it, Laboon.
You can't afford to beat
yourself up anymore.
There's only a tiny
amount of sedative left,
and until I can make some
more, you'll have to make nuts.
I've told you before, that wall
divides the world's oceans.
It doesn't matter how
many times you hit it.
It won't break, not even for
someone as mighty as you.
I don't claim to speak whale, but
it seems to have calmed down a bit.
Seems that way.
Now, we saved your lives for the time being,
but you better talk and make it quick.
Mr.
Nine, these heathens are pirates.
Yes, that's painfully
obvious, Miss Wednesday.
But if we speak to their humanity and
compassion, they should understand our plight.
Maybe.
You parasites are still here.
I grow weary of this,
and for the last time,
as long as I draw breath, you will not
lay a single harmful finger on Laboon.
He's back again.
Who's the old guy?
You can't bully us into
abandoning our mission.
We were sent here to hunt this whale, and
that's exactly what we're going to do.
And this time we won't let you interfere.
We're about to give this
whale a new blowhole!
Fire, baby!
Let's...
He jumped straight into the
line of fire! Did he just...
Was he protecting the whale?
Your defiance is pointless. Go ahead!
Waste your time!
But make no mistake, that hulking
beast will provide food for our town!
What's going on?
What was that for?
I just...
wanted to hit him.
I thank you for saving my life,
though I must ask, why did you do it?
I wasn't trying to save you.
There was just something
about those two I didn't like.
Okay, I think it's time
we got some answers.
Who are these guys?
And how did you end up inside this whale?
These two are thugs from a nearby
town looking for whale meat.
If they caught him,
Laboon could feed the townspeople
for at least two or three years easy.
All they're concerned with is
filling their fat, greedy bellies
Laboon?
That's the whale's name.
He's a unique and magnificent creature.
An island whale, one of the
largest species in the world.
That can only be found in the West Blue.
I won't allow them to
slaughter him for food.
It's a shame that he's stuck
here so far away from his domain.
You see, there's a reason he keeps
hitting himself on the red line.
And howling at Reverse Mountain.
There is?
Yes,
to put it one way Inside Laboon's
body beats the heart of a human He has
most impatiently awaited And is eternally
devoted to a certain band of pirates
Going on 50 long years now Listen closely
And I will reveal to you
Laboon's tragic story
One fine sunny day While I was fulfilling
my duties as the lighthouse keeper Some
good-natured pirates came down Reverse
Mountain They were followed by a baby whale,
Spry and Chipper Whom I would soon
come to know as the one and only Laboon
He is an island whale,
one of the largest in the world They are a
rare species found only in the West Blue.
Laboon had developed a
bond with the pirates,
traveling with them for
much of their journey.
But knowing the dangers of the Grand Line,
the pirates chose to leave
Laboon behind in the West Blue.
But the stubborn little
whale followed them anyway.
As a general rule,
island whales are social animals and
travel together in family groups.
I suspect that Laboon had somehow come to
feel that those pirates were his family.
The wear and tear on the
pirate's ship was quite severe,
so they stayed here for several months.
In that time, I, too, was able to
forge a close relationship with them.
Thus, when the day of their
departure finally arrived...
I have a favor to ask
of you, my dear friend.
Could you look after
Laboon for a few years?
When my men and I have completed our
voyage around the world, we'll be back.
Listen to me, Laboon.
We're taking our ship to
the end of the Grand Line.
Until we return, I need you to
wait for us here with Crocus.
You can't come with us.
It's too dangerous, even
for a mighty whale like you.
Don't worry, three years
will pass by like a flash.
And don't forget, no matter the
distance, our friendship lasts forever.
Well, I guess it's time.
All right, men!
We're setting sail!
Hoist the anchor! Yeah!
Laboon!
You have to wait for us here
and mine Crocus, Laboon!
Don't worry, we'll be back! I promise!
That was 50 long years ago.
50 years?
So Laboon has been waiting all this
time for his friends to return?
No wonder he's upset.
That kind of wait would
drive anyone crazy.
This is some canal. Wow.
Amazing this whale's still alive
with a hole like this in his body.
I suppose you're responsible for this?
Just a doctor's playful
mind. Doctor? That's right.
Legally certified.
I also ran a clinic on
the Cape once upon a time.
Before that, I served as a ship's doctor.
Really?
That's great! Then join us!
We need a doctor!
Don't be ridiculous.
I no longer have that kind of energy.
Exploring the seas is a young man's bird!
What kind of a doctor hollows
out the inside of a whale?
Maybe it's part of the treatment
the girl is right with a creature of
this size It's virtually impossible to
treat it from the outside therefore.
I devised a more drastic solution.
Here's the exit
What is it?
Don't you think 50 years is a bit extreme?
Those pirates sure know how
to test someone's patience.
Idiot, don't you get it?
This is the Grand Line.
His friends are dead.
That whale can wait forever.
They won't be back.
Why are you all being so pessimistic?
You don't know that they're dead.
They could still come back for him.
Come on, have some sympathy, will you?
I thought it was very touching.
I mean, a whale still believing a promise
his friends made despite all these years?
That's a true bond, right, Pops? Indeed.
But the lesson here is
that reality is cruel.
Laboon's cohorts aren't dead.
The truth is they abandoned their quest.
I learned that they turned
tail and left the Grand Line.
I don't believe it.
I mean, why abandon him like that?
You say they ran away from the Grand Line.
Do you know if they made it
through the Calm Belt alive?
I can't claim to know
exactly what became of them,
but I doubt they'll ever
come back here again.
Seasons, weather,
currents, wind direction.
On the Grand Line, these elements
seem to defy the very laws of nature.
Common sense is useless, and the terror
of that fact can be quite overwhelming.
So if I've got this straight,
what you're saying is?
These pirates were a bunch of cowards!
Who cared more about
saving their own asses?
than keeping a promise to a friend.
Why would anyone abandon
such a loyal creature?
Just look at him.
It's cruelty on a grand scale.
But if you've known all this,
why haven't you told him?
Laboon can obviously communicate with you.
He seems to understand humans
quite well for a whale.
I did tell him, down to
the last miserable detail.
I know this isn't what you want
to hear, but it's the truth.
Your friends left the Grand Line.
The bond you shared with
each other was real.
Just as real as the promise they
made to return for you one day.
But still, face the facts.
Those men are never coming back.
Laboon, please, I say
this for your own good.
They're not coming back!
I understand that you
don't want to accept it.
But you need to realize
that this is how things are.
Listen?
Laboon!
That was the day that Laboon
began to howl at Reverse Mountain.
Soon after he started slamming
his body against the red line.
It's as if he believes that wall
is what keeps his friends away?
And by breaking it, he can
clear the path for their return!
I admire his dedication.
Never gave up on him.
He refuses to believe me because then
he'd have to admit that it's over!
And that terrifies him more than anything.
There's no way for him to
go back to the West Blue.
So what we have is a paradox
of tragic proportions?
Laboon is a lost soul dying
to live with his friends.
But won't stop killing
himself to reach them.
Tragedy.
Still, for all the grief those
pirates put him through,?
they did the same to you by
saddling you with their burden.
I mean, you've done enough
for Laboon. What about you?
The scars on his hide are deep.
Those in his heart are even deeper.
He needs someone to tend his
wounds, and I'm all he's got.
For years, he's battered himself
while I've patched him up.
A strange friendship, but it works.
What the hell is that idiot up to?
We gotta watch him every second.
We've been watching
him, look what happens.
Gum-Gum!
Flowing Rage Lens!
You think he's aware that that's our mast?
And now it's on top of a whale.
Why'd he do that?
Hey, Luffy, stop tearing up the ship!
You pass!
Luffy, stop!
The boy! He's dead! Oh, don't worry.
It'll take way more
than that to kill Luffy.
Gotcha!
What does he think he's doing?
You want to let us in on your
plan before you kill yourself?
It's a draw.
I'm stronger than I look.
I can always tell when
someone's itching to fight.
Well, if you want a battle,
I'll gladly give you one.
Your shipmates used to
spar with you, didn't they?
And you miss it.
Well, I can rival anything
they threw at you.
Tell you what,
after me and my friends travel the Grand
Line, we'll come back here and find you.
And then you better be
ready for a rematch.
Hey, not bad!
Consider this a symbol of my
promise to come do battle with you.
Of course, it's a rush paint job,
so you'll have to be careful
and avoid hitting your head,
or you'll rub it off, understand?
Goodwill!
Where are they?
Where are who?
Oh, you mean those two weirdos?
I guess they escaped.
Must have happened when we
were distracted by Laboon.
I wonder who they were.
Miss Wednesday, what
are we going to do now?
First, put some distance between us and
these morons, then we report to the boss.
Our time for completing this
mission has long since run out.
I can hear the others now.
They're probably already
calling us traitors.
I know, but without our weapons,
we've no choice but to go back
to the office and start over.
And this time, no one will stop us!
Oh no, I couldn't have! What is it?
It's... gone. What?
What's this thing?
How could you have lost the log? Pose?
I don't know.
I must have dropped it somewhere.
But we're not going anywhere without it.
No.
This can't. It won't be happening!
Oh no!
The Unluckies!
We're out of time! Mr.
Thirteen! It's Friday!
Don't be hasty!
Please, we can explain!
We'll check in with Buzz immediately!
Okay, then,
I finally have some
peace and quiet so I can
work on a plan for the Grand Line journey.
I don't think I forgot about
you, elephant bluefin tuna.
Gee, that's my life.
If he breaks it, then
I put it back together.
Hey, get off your lazy
butt and give me a hand.
This ship isn't going
to fix itself, you know.
You mind? Keep it down.
Is there some problem, my dearest Nami?
If it's food you're
worried about, say no more.
Someone say food?
You idiot!
The compass is broken.
The needle just spins.
It won't stop.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I don't know about you,
but I'm getting dizzy.
Whoa, this is cool.
It is sadly apparent that
none of you possess the
slightest knowledge about
how things work here.
Did you all come here to die?
Great spread.
It's for everyone.
There is nothing wrong with your compass.
The Grand Line has little
regard for the rules of the sea.
Common sense is useless in this place.
The needle?
Why does it spin?
Because we are surrounded by
a powerful magnetic field.
The islands here are riddled
with magnetic minerals,
which cause all sorts of abnormalities.
Also, the winds and currents
lack constancy in their patterns.
As a navigator, I'm sure you
can appreciate this dilemma.
So then, if we don't have a way to tell
direction, this whole trip is hopeless.
I don't know what to say. We're screwed.
Hey, you're the navigator,
so navigate us out of here.
This is delicious.
You ought to try some.
But all of you just shut up for five
seconds so I can figure this out.
This noise of the elephant tuna
is my favorite part, tasty.
If you have any hope of
navigating the Grand Line,
you're going to need a
Log Pose to guide you.
Log Pose?
I've never heard of it.
It's a specially designed compass
that can record levels of magnetism.
Is it strange looking?
Why, yes, it does have an odd shape.
Something like this?
Yes, exactly.
Only a fool courting disaster would attempt
to travel the Grand Line without one.
Understood.
Excuse me for one second.
So.
Why didn't you tell me you
had one of those log things?
I found it on deck just laying there.
Those two weirdos must have
dropped it when they escaped.
Did they?
Why'd you hit me? Felt like it. Oh, okay.
Huh, but there isn't a
dial face on this thing.
You don't need one.
It's a special brand of magnetism that
runs through the Grand Line Islands,
complete with its own set of rules
that makes it possible to get around.
By recording the level of
magnetism between two islands,
you can chart a route from
one island to the next.
The Log Pose method is
really the only choice,
since the magnetism here presents huge
problems for conventional navigation.
As it turns out, Reverse Mountain
is a great starting point.
It produces seven levels of magnetism,
but it doesn't matter which
one you choose to start with.
Eventually, all of them will pull
against each other and form one route.
And the island at the end
of that route is Raftel,
The last and most mysterious
in the Grand Line.
Its very existence was confirmed
by the King of the Pirates,
the only known person to have traveled
the Grand Line in its entirety.
Raftel. That's it!
That must be where the
One Piece is hidden!
That's the most prominent theory.
But no one's been able to set
foot on Raftel Island since.
Don't worry, we'll know soon enough.
Well, I'm satisfied.
You guys ready to go?
I told you that was for all of us!
He even ate the bones.
A Log Pose.
We have to take special care of this.
It's the key to finding the
greatest treasure of all time.
You greedy, bottomless pit, you
ate the meal I made for Nami.
Well, I hope you left
room for your dessert!
Ow.
Why's everyone hitting me?
You never think of anyone
but yourself and...
Sanchi? Yes?
Both of you, get out of my
sight before I wring your neck!
Okay, so,
correct me if I'm wrong, but doesn't the
Log Pose work better when it's not broken?
Oh, no.
Our Log Pose is ruined. Calm yourselves.
I will give you my own.
As a thank you for helping Laboon.
Oh, good, I'm not dead.
Hello, dear lady.
Allow me to help you to your feet.
Oh, thank you.
Nice day, don't you think?
Hey, we need a favor.
Whiskey Peak?
Huh, that's a funny name.
So, what is it?
That's where we live, um, sir.
How are you stranded?
Where's your ship?
Well, it was destroyed.
Asking us for a ride is pushing it, Mr.
Nine, especially after
you try to kill the whale.
What's with the wardrobe?
What are you supposed to be?
I am a king!
You're lying! No, please!
We can't say! She's right!
You have to believe us!
Our only motive here is getting home!
We'd tell you everything if
we could, it's just that...
Mystery is our company's motto!
You see, we have to be
mysterious, it's sort of a rule.
We have confidence in your character.
Can't you give us the same courtesy?
Please, we're begging you,
show some mercy. Don't do it.
These two fools are dishonest to the core.
They can't be trusted.
Listen,
I should mention that our Log Pose was
broken and we don't have another one,
so still want to ride with us?
What? You broke it? That was mine!
Those aren't cheap, you know!
You're stuck here, too?
How long were you going to make us
back before you bothered to tell us?
Oh, sorry. I forgot.
Crocus gave us his Log Pose, so...
No, please have pity on us.
That lousy bitch, she tricked us.
It's fine, you can ride with us.
You said your home is called Whiskey Peak?
Let's go there.
Why?
These two are obviously some
pretty shady characters.
Why would we take them anywhere?
It's fine.
Don't sweat the small stuff.
We'll be all right.
Choose your route carefully.
Once you head out from here,
you'll be committed to that course.
That's okay.
If we don't like it, we'll try
a different route next time.
I see.
Okay, it's time we get going!
Now that me and Laboon have an understanding,
I can leave with a clear conscience.
Just who on earth do you
think you are, anyway?
Was that me?
Oh, i'm the man who'll
be king of the pirates
Not too bright, this one
Should be good to go The Log Pose
has had plenty of time to store the
route The needle should be pointing
in the same direction as the map.
It's pointing directly to Whiskey Peak.
See ya, Pops!
Thanks again for the lock pose!
Take care!
Have a safe trip, my boy!
I'm off, Laboon!
Be ready to fight when I get back!
Next up, Whiskey Peak!
Ready, gang?
Let's set sail!
I wonder,
Luffy and his exuberant crew could be
the very pirates we've been waiting for.
That young captain sure
has a way about him.
It's uncanny, really.
Wouldn't you agree, Roger?
Oh, you've got me heart and soul.
I wrote you a love song
to let you know that I.
Wanna be with you till the end of time!
Even when the sparkles fade!
And doubts invade our
one still trusting light?
I promise you that I will stay.
We'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies.
We built a castle of sand.
And now we're watching it wash away.
It doesn't have to end!
We'll start again, this time round.
We'll build a stronger love.
Oh, you've got me heart and soul.
I just wanna hold you and not let go.
You know that I'll be with
you till the end of time.
Oh, you've got me heart and soul.